# INEZ GRANT

321 Main Street, Seattle, WA 32109 i.grant@youremail.com (901) 234-5678 Seasoned library page with over five years of professional experience supporting student services and providing administrative assistance in academic libraries. Diligent and hardworking with exceptional attention to detail and a drive to go above and beyond expectations. Outstanding working knowledge of library best practices and a proven track record for maintaining attractive, organized research environments.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Seattle Central College, Seattle, WA | September 2018 - Present

- Assist librarians in delivering informational literacy sessions and student orientations
- Promote the library's outreach projects to students and provide support during events and author lectures
- Inspect returned materials for damage, arranging repairs and issuing fines when necessary according to the college's policies
- Maintain tidy and organized shelves and public areas and sort books ready for shelving

#### LIBRARY PAGE

University of Washington, Seattle, WA | July 2015 - September 2018

- Supervised students in the library's computer suite and assisted with using the online resource catalogs
- Advised students on the location of print and digital resources and fetched items from the closed storerooms
- Provided support at the front desk during busy periods, issuing loans and receiving returns
- Inspected the library regularly for tidiness and safety and reported health and safety concerns to the maintenance team

## **EDUCATION**

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS IN LITERATURE AND SOCIETY

South Seattle College, Seattle, Wa | September 2013 - June 2015

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Strong knowledge of digital resource databases
- Excellent understanding of Dewey decimal system
- Friendly and professional customer service style
- Collaborative and independent working
- Punctual and reliable